<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-08-26T17:03:47-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Nabeel Eledroos</title><subtitle>A Computer Science student at UMass Amherst, with an interest in all sorts of things.</subtitle><author><name>Nabeel Eledroos</name><email>nabeel@eledroos.net</email></author><entry><title type="html">Welcome!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/08/15/my-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome!" /><published>2019-08-15T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2019-08-15T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/08/15/my-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/08/15/my-blog/">&lt;p&gt;My name is Nabeel Eledroos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;data/hackumass.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s me in the back left, working on a gesture controlled car at &lt;a href=&quot;https://hackumass.com&quot;&gt;HackUMass&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am currently a Junior Computer Science student UMass Amherst, interested in a wide variety of disciplines within computer science such as computer vision, cybersecurity, and embedded programming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a look at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/nabeel-eledroos&quot;&gt;my GitHub page&lt;/a&gt; to see a portfolio of projects that I have worked on. Please feel free to check out my LinkedIn as well as download my resume on the sidebar to the left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;contact-me&quot;&gt;Contact Me&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can email me at: &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nabeel@eledroos.net&quot;&gt;nabeel@eledroos.net&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Nabeel Eledroos</name><email>nabeel@eledroos.net</email></author><summary type="html">My name is Nabeel Eledroos. That’s me in the back left, working on a gesture controlled car at HackUMass. I am currently a Junior Computer Science student UMass Amherst, interested in a wide variety of disciplines within computer science such as computer vision, cybersecurity, and embedded programming. Take a look at my GitHub page to see a portfolio of projects that I have worked on. Please feel free to check out my LinkedIn as well as download my resume on the sidebar to the left. Contact Me You can email me at: nabeel@eledroos.net.</summary></entry></feed>